{
    "id": "e9f1b624509a447a8d542aba7d0715c6",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "They held a press conference last week to ……………………….. support for their proposal.",
            "description": "To drum up support is to gain support. ",
            "answers": [
                "drum up",
                "muck in",
                "mull over"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c153014bc12242f7aceb35ee72527724"
        },
        {
            "question": "The deal ………………………. at the last minute for reasons that were not clear.",
            "description": "If a deal falls through, it fails and it is abandoned.",
            "answers": [
                "fell out",
                "fell through",
                "fell off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d9faec3543ee4afd935cfaf20a5ab4da"
        },
        {
            "question": "He .............................. the channels hoping to find something interesting.",
            "description": "To flip through is to change from one channel to another. Flick through has the same meaning.",
            "answers": [
                "flipped through",
                "flicked through",
                "fell through"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5029343396c24cfcaf1efbdd7d546e3e"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is not uncommon for people to ………………………… alternative medicine when modern drugs don’t work.",
            "description": "When you fall back on something/somebody you turn to it/them when you are in difficulty.",
            "answers": [
                "fall behind on",
                "fall back on",
                "fall for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "043867f313cb432fac5f8cf8eda5fd7e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The word .......................... that she was having an affair with her boss.",
            "description": "When news gets around, it spreads.",
            "answers": [
                "got about",
                "got away",
                "got around"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "eb113ff782654897850a282743f4cca3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is not a bright student and he doesn’t do well in his tests. He just manages to ........................",
            "description": "To get by is to live on very little money, or to manage to do something with difficulty.",
            "answers": [
                "get off",
                "get in",
                "get by"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "94071647daa74db1b0d62b2459eadafc"
        },
        {
            "question": "The meat smells awful. It must have .............................",
            "description": "If meat goes off, it is not good anymore.",
            "answers": [
                "gone out",
                "gone off",
                "gone about"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a020def48b2747e7bea5730dcdc2def1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Legal battles are slow and expensive. In many cases, the appeals process ………………………….. for years.",
            "description": "If something drags on, it lasts longer than necessary.",
            "answers": [
                "drags out",
                "drags off",
                "drags on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7dc60ad73ad24893954f4e5b275bd0c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was tired and ....................... while watching TV",
            "description": "To drop off is to fall asleep. Doze off has the same meaning.",
            "answers": [
                "dozed off",
                "dozed down",
                "dropped off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f1be1be7c4254aa8832d6429c3726660"
        },
        {
            "question": "Human rights activists have been asking the government to ............................. the death penalty.",
            "description": "To do away with something is to abolish it.",
            "answers": [
                "do in",
                "do away",
                "do away with",
                "do out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "77188aff043548898d714bb911336899"
        },
        {
            "question": "I think it was the lack of sleep more than the drinks that really …………………………..",
            "description": " When something does you in, it makes you tired.",
            "answers": [
                "did me away",
                "did me up",
                "did me in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c6dfa2f80a204bbe8b08c37373e2175e"
        },
        {
            "question": "His marriage ………………………….. when his wife discovered that he had been cheating on her.",
            "description": "When things fall apart, they disintegrate or break into pieces. When relationships fall apart, they fail to work.",
            "answers": [
                "fell off",
                "fell down",
                "fell apart"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0676d695f86f4410976c2649ec99e046"
        }
    ]
}